al-imam al-zahabi,
rahimahullah, looked at a
of the Quran where Allah said
subhanahu wa ta'ala, in
tajtanibu kaba'iru ma
tunhawna anhu, nu kafir ankum
say'atikum
wa nu dkhilkum mudkhalan
kareema,
in tajtanibu kaba'iru ma
tunhawna anhu,
oh mankind if you abstain
oh people of iman if you
abstain
in tajtanibu kaba'iru ma
tunhawna anhu,
if you abstain from those
that are
kaba'ir
from the things that we have
prohibited
you, from the things that we
have
prohibited you, some of them
are kaba'ir
in tajtanibu kaba'iru ma
tunhawna anhu,
if you abstain from those
that are
kaba'ir
amongst the things that you
have been
prohibited from, Allah said
the reward is
that nu kafir anhum
say'atikum
your smaller, your relatively
lesser sins,
nu kafir, Allah said nu kafir
anhum,
we will atone for you
your smaller sins, those sins
that are
of lesser gravity than al
kaba'ir,
they are also called
alsogha'ir
they are also called allamam,
nu kafir anhum say'atikum,
they are also called say'at
we will make you also gain a
honorable entrance into that
home of esteem
al jannah